Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society institutional records ARC.288
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 7: Curatorial Affairs and Collections, 1862-2020
  - Sub-series 7.2: Library Department Files, 1863-2019, bulk 1980-2007
    - Deaccessioning [Correspondence], 2005 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Deborah Schwartz Profile, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Library Visitor Totals, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Mellon Foundation, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - [New York Archives Week], 2005 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - NY Times Art and Leisure, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - [Partners for a Nation of Learners], 2005 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - PastPerfect, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Plymouth Church Workshop, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Questor Systems -- ARGUS, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - [Weekly Planner], 2005 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Ottaway Family [Resarch], 1997-1998, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Auctions and Other Collection Possibilities, 1999-2000, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Lefferts Papers, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 16-17)
    - Weeksville Society Archives, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 1-3)
    - Archivists Round Table, 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Library Programs, 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
    - Library Subscriptions, 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - [Newspaper Clippings], 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Rare Books Collection, 2004-2006 (Box 44, Folder 1-3)
      Includes notes, lists, and correspondence.
    - Reference Statistics, 2004-2006 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Storage Correspondence, 2004-2006 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Underground Railroad Peer Review, 2004-2006 (Box 44, Folder 6-8)
      Contains 2 CDs.
    - [Archives and Manuscripts] Problems, 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Book Orders, 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Collection Codes, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Fashion Institute of Technology, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Harlem Downing, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Library Programs, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Microfilm Newspapers, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Microfilm Reader, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - NYU Contract [Drafts], 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 8-10)
    - NYU Contract Comments, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - [Reference Statistics], 2005 September-2006 August (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report Items, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Archivists Toolkit, circa 2006 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Auto Reply Message, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Bibliographical Society of America, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Books to Catalog, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Cataloging Issues -- NYU, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Donald Simon Books, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - EAD 101 [Slideshow Print-Outs], 2006 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - East Flatbush Guide, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Green-Wood Cemetery National Historic Register [Lecture], 2006 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - It Happened in Brooklyn, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Kane Street Synagogue, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Lectures in the Library, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Library Dinner, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Lott Family Materials, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Montauk Matter, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - NYU Agreement, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Processing Priorities, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Reference Statistics, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Sweet'N Low, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Upcoming Government Deadlines, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Visitor Services, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Central Brooklyn Jazz Consortium, 2007 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - GATEWAI, 2004-2007 (Box 47, Folder 1-5)
      The Graduate Archives Training and Education: Work and Information (GATEWAI) program was a collaboration between Pratt SILS and the Brooklyn Historical Society. It provided low-income and minority students with scholarships and experience through internships at BHS.
    - Invoices, 2005-2007 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Objects for Possible Web Use, circa 2005-2007 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn Museum, 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Image Database, circa 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Grant Planning, 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Library Programs, 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Mellon Foundation, 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Scholars Council, 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - African-American Family Research [Workshop], 2007 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoriation Corporation, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Heights Seminary, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - The Brooklynite [Research], 2007 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Goldman Sachs, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Library Opening [Marilyn Petit Speech], 2007 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - [Library Re-opening Invitation], 2007 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Library Schematic, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Loans and Exhibits, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - METRO, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Mosley Collection [Correspondence], 2007 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Reference Statistics, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - The Roots of Modern Brooklyn [Conference], 2007 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Workshops, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Fulton Street Mall, Schematic Design -- Round 3.1, 2007 (Box 504, Folder 2)
    - Dock Street DUMBO Project, ULURP Application to City Planning Commission, 2008 (Box 504, Folder 2)
    - Othmer Bequest, 1996-1997, 2004-2008 (Box 48, Folder 14-16)
    - New York State Conservation Program, 1998, 2004, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Donation Inquiries, 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Potential Donations, 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Grant Planning, 2007-2008 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Ethical Deaccessioning [Research], 2008 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Goldman Sachs [Purchase Orders], 2008 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Interpreting Brooklyn Workshop [Agenda], 2008 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - [Leilani Dawson] Meeting Minutes / Memos / Notes, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Map Cataloging [Notes], 2008 (Box 49, Folder 6-8)
    - Network to Freedom, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Print Room Info, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Server Storage, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - [Arthur Lonto, railroad collection], 2008 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Map Cataloging [Research], 2001-2009 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Blog Recommendations, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      Contains 1 CD.
    - IMLS Bookshelf, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Potential Donations, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Blog Stats, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn Law School, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Goldman Sachs Volunteer Day, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Grant Feedback, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - ALEPH / NYU [Services Agreement], 2006-2010 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - In Pursuit of Freedom, 2008-2010 (Box 50, Folder 9-10)
    - Rare Book Requests, 2009-2010 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Bureau of Sewers, circa 2010 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Goldman Sachs Volunteer Day, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Hidden Collections Symposium, 2010 March (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - NYU Agreement, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - OCLC, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Clancy Surveys, 2008-2011 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - NYU Cataloging -- Exlibris, 2008-2011 (Box 51, Folder 1-4)
    - NYU -- Primo 3, 2008-2011 (Box 51, Folder 5-7)
    - National Book Auction, 2009-2011 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Leon Levy Funding, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Proposed Deaccessions, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Telephone Features, circa 2011 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Vendors, 2009-2012 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Book Orders, 2010-2012 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Goldman Sachs [Purchase Orders], 2011-2012 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - John D. Locke Bust, 2011-2012 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Project Cataloger Files, 2011-2012 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Includes work plans, meeting minutes, and correspondence.
    - Gilder Lehrman, 2012 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Leonard Rosenfeld, 2012 (Box 52, Folder 6-8)
      Contains 9 optical discs.
    - Rejected Donations, 2011-2013 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Crossing Borders, Bridging Generations, 2013-2014 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - BobCat Cataloging Edits, 2014 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Long Island Star Digitization, 2014-2015 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Rejected Donations, 2016 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Archival Cleaning [Invoice], 2018 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - [Brooklyn Museum Donations], 1998, 2019 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      Includes scans of documents from the registrar's office at the Brooklyn Museum concerning donations from the Long Island Historical Society that occurred in the 1920s.
    - Digital Collections [Meeting Notes], 2019 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Packer Collegiate Institute [Costs], 2019 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Sub-series 7.3: Librarian's Reports, 1874-1989, bulk 1890-1961
    Sub-series 7.3: Librarian's Reports contains reports that document the activities of the library for a given year. The reports include updates on cataloging and reference work, new acquisitions, financial gifts, membership changes, attendance, special exhibitions, personnel changes, and expenditures of library funds.
    - [Librarian's Report], 1863 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1864-1865 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1866-1867 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1874 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1877 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Librarian's Reports, 1890-1899 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Librarian's Reports, 1900-1910 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Librarian's Reports, 1910-1919 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Librarian's Reports, 1920-1929 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Librarian's Reports, 1930-1939 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Librarian's Reports, 1940-1949 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Librarian's Reports, 1950-1959 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Librarian's Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report: Librarian's, 1960-1964 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1965 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1981 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1982 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1984 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1985 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - [Librarian's Report], 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Sub-series 7.4: Library Correspondence, 1862-2007
    To protect patron privacy, the following materials are temporarily restricted:
    Materials dated 1951-1960 are closed for research until 2035. Materials dated 1961-1970 are closed for research until 2045. Materials dated 1971-1980 are closed for research until 2055. Materials dated 1981-1990 are closed for research until 2065. Materials dated 1991-2000 are closed for research until 2075. Materials dated 2001-2007 are closed for research until 2085.
    Sub-series 7.4: Library Correspondence contains incoming and outgoing correspondence of the library spanning from 1862 to 2007. The early correspondence documents various topics such as donations, publication exchanges, membership acceptances and resignations, lecture invitations, and meetings. Many of these letters originate from museums, universities, public libraries, historical societies, banks, booksellers, and individuals seeking assistance with their research. Prominent institutions include The Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences (specifically the Brooklyn Museum), The New York Public Library, the Bond and Mortgage Guarantee Company, and over 30 historical and genealogical societies across the United States.
    After 1940, the correspondence primarily consists of reference inquiries regarding genealogy, building history, and local historical topics. These letters also contain information related to memberships, loans, and sales of publications.
    - [Library Correspondence], 1862-1863 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1864 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1865 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1866 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1867 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1868 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1869 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1870 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1871 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1872 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1873 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1874 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1875 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1876 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1877 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1878 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1879 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1880 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1881 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1882 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1883 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1884 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1885 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1886 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1887 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1888 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1889 (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1890 (Box 57, Folder 3-4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1891 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1892 (Box 57, Folder 6-7)
    - Deutsch Correspondence, 1892 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      Contains incoming correspondence from The Deutsch Lithographing and Printing Company.
    - [Library Correspondence], 1893 (Box 57, Folder 9-10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1894 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1895 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1896 (Box 58, Folder 2-3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1897 (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1898 (Box 58, Folder 6-7)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1899 (Box 58, Folder 8-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1900 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1901 (Box 59, Folder 3-5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1902 (Box 59, Folder 6-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1903 (Box 59, Folder 9-10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1904 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1905 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1906 (Box 60, Folder 5-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1907 (Box 60, Folder 7-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1908 (Box 60, Folder 9-10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1909 (Box 61, Folder 1-3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1910 (Box 61, Folder 4-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1911 (Box 61, Folder 7-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1912 (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1913 (Box 62, Folder 4-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1914 (Box 62, Folder 7-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1915 (Box 63, Folder 1-3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1916 (Box 63, Folder 4-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1917 (Box 63, Folder 7-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1918 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1919 (Box 64, Folder 3-5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1920 (Box 64, Folder 6-7)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1921 (Box 64, Folder 8-10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1922 (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1923 (Box 65, Folder 3-5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1924 (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1925 (Box 66, Folder 4-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1926 (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1927 (Box 67, Folder 5-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1928 (Box 68, Folder 1-4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1929 (Box 68, Folder 5-8)
    - [The Institute of American Genealogy], 1929-1936 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1930 (Box 69, Folder 2-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1931 (Box 69, Folder 7-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1931 (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1932 (Box 70, Folder 3-7)
    - Washington Miniature, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      Correspondence pertaining to sending the Peale Miniature to Washington, D.C.
    - [Library Correspondence], 1933 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1933 (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1934 (Box 71, Folder 4-7)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1935 (Box 72, Folder 1-5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1936 (Box 72, Folder 6-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1936 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1937 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1938-1941 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1938 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1939 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1940 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1941 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1942 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1943 (Box 73, Folder 9-14)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1944 (Box 74, Folder 1-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1945 (Box 74, Folder 7-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1945 (Box 75, Folder 1-5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1946 (Box 75, Folder 6-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1946 (Box 76, Folder 1-4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1947 (Box 76, Folder 5-10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1947 (Box 77, Folder 1-4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1948 (Box 77, Folder 5-10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1948 (Box 78, Folder 1-3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1949 (Box 78, Folder 4-10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1949 (Box 79, Folder 1-5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1950 (Box 79, Folder 6-10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1950 (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1951 (Box 80, Folder 5-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1951 (Box 81, Folder 1-3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1952 (Box 81, Folder 4-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1952 (Box 82, Folder 1-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1953 (Box 82, Folder 7-10)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1953 (Box 83, Folder 1-4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1954 (Box 83, Folder 5-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1954 (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1955 (Box 84, Folder 5-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1955 (Box 85, Folder 1-3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1956 (Box 85, Folder 4-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1956 (Box 86, Folder 1-5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1957 (Box 86, Folder 6-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1957 (Box 87, Folder 1-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1958 (Box 87, Folder 7-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1958 (Box 88, Folder 1-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1959 (Box 89, Folder 1-7)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1960 (Box 89, Folder 8-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1960 (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1961 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1961 May-1961 October (Box 90, Folder 4-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1961 October-1962 April (Box 91, Folder 1-6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1962 May-1962 October (Box 91, Folder 7-8)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1962 May-1962 October (Box 92, Folder 1-5)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1962 October-1963 April (Box 92, Folder 6-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1962 October-1963 April (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1963 May-1963 December (Box 93, Folder 3-9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1963 May-1963 December (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Library Correspondence, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Military Collection Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - [Harriet Stryker-Rodda Correspondence], 1965-1967 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      Mrs. Harriet Stryker-Rodda was a genealogist, historian, and LIHS volunteer. In 1963, the LIHS Board of Directors hired her as the Society's archivist to manage the library during a period of transition, which included a change of leadership and the total loss of staff.
    - Book Orders Received, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 6-7)
    - Book Orders Received, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Requests, Bills [and] Gifts, 1967-1971 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1968-1969 (Box 94, Folder 10-11)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1968-1969 (Box 95, Folder 1-4)
    - Genealogy Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 95, Folder 5-9)
    - Genealogy Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 96, Folder 1-4)
    - Historical Inquiries, 1968-1970 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Books for Sale, 1969-1970 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Missing Newspapers, 1969-1970 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Exchanges, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Genealogy Correspondence, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 9-10)
    - Genealogy Correspondence, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 1-3)
    - Historical Inquiries, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 4-6)
    - Miscellaneous -- Inquiries, Acknowledgments, Letters of Correction, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Missing Newspapers, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Orders, Bills, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Our Requests, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Genealogy Correspondence, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Genealogy Correspondence, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 1-7)
    - Historical Inquiries, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Historical Inquiries, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Inquiries, Acknowledgments, Letters of Correction, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Missing Newspapers, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Orders, Bills, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Our Requests, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Research Letters, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Historical Inquiries, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 8-11)
    - Missing Periodicals, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Genealogical Inquiries, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 1-4)
    - Historical Inquiries, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 5-8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Acknowledgments, Letters of Correction, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Inquiries, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Missing Periodicals, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Our Requests, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Print Collection Correspondence, 1954-1974 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Genealogical Inquiries, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 2-7)
    - Historical Inquiries, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 1-3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Acknowledgments, Letters of Correction, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous -- Inquiries, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Missing Periodicals, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Our Requests, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Genealogical Inquiries, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 8-12)
    - Genealogical Inquiries, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 1-5)
    - Historical Inquiries, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 6-8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Inquiries, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Genealogical Correspondence, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 1-6)
    - Historical Inquiries, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1-5)
    - Correspondence Relating to Print Collection, 1977-1978 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - [Library Correspondence], 1978 (Box 106, Folder 1-8)
    - [Outgoing Correspondence], 1978 February (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - [Outgoing Correspondence], 1978 March (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - [Outgoing Correspondence], 1978 April (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - [Outgoing Correspondence], 1978 May (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - [Outgoing Correspondence], 1978 June (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - [Outgoing Correspondence], 1978 July (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - [Outgoing Correspondence], 1978 August (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - [Outgoing Correspondence], 1979 January (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Library Correspondence, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 9-14)
    - Library Correspondence, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 1-3)
    - Thanks to Staff, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Book Orders Received, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Library Correspondence, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 6-7)
    - Library Correspondence, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 1-8)
    - Thank You Letters, 1980-1981 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Binding Received, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Book Orders Received, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 3)